gsmhelpful.com 2018-03-27

# Privacy Policy / Gsm Helpful | All You Need for Mobile Flashing & GSM

Privacy Policy– Terms Of Use  

##  **Privacy Policy For  ** **www.gsmhelpful.com**

For any quarries or any information for privacy policy, please feel free to contact us on gsmxda@gmail.com. It is very important for us of the privacy policy at  **http://gsmhelpful.com/.** in this policy,it shows the types of information which is received and also collected by  **http://gsmhelpful.com/**  and also shows that how it is used.

##  **Google Advertising Cookie and  Double Click DART cookie and Privacy Policies: **

Google can use to serve its add as a third party vendor.Google can use the DART cookie to serve ads for the visitors who visits our website. Users may use the DART cookie and ads which is provided by google for our privacy policy.

##  **Links:**

The other website frequently links to our website  **http://gsmhelpful.com/**. for any content or business practices we are not at all responsible for it. We request you to visit our website and read privacy policy.this privacy policy applies the information collected by  **http://gsmhelpful.com/**

##  **Disclaimer:**

We are not at all connected with any cell phone companies such as Nokia, Samsung, Sony Ericsson, Samsung, Lg and Motorola they are the properties of their respective owners. Only for study and information purpose, we provide it.

##  **We are not responsible for any damage or loss:**

Atleast one member of our team has checked all post that we post in our website. We are not at all responsible if something is damage or lost. Do any ting on your own risk.
